http://www.mediapost.com/privacy/

Toggle navigationNewsCurrent StoriesMediaPost HomeToday's NewsToday's OpinionsMediaPost Week in ReviewAgencies &The Agency BusinessMediaPost's Agency DailyMEDIApsssstAccounts in ReviewOut to LaunchPeople on the MoveMAD - LondonFuturesAI & IoT DailyConnected ThinkingCRISIS REPORTCovid-19 ImpactDigital Media, Marketingand AdvertisingDigital News DailyData & Programmatic InsiderMobile InsiderSocial InsiderVideo InsiderRTBlogPolicyBlogEmail Marketing DailyEmail InsiderSearch & Performance Marketing DailyInside PerformanceResearchResearch IntelligencerCenter for Marketing & Media ResearchMedia Buying/PlanningMediaDailyNewsMedia InsiderTelevisionTelevisionNewsDailyTVBlogTV WatchAdvanced TV InsiderPublishing & PublishersPublishers DailyPublishing InsiderNative InsiderBrand and Product MarketingMarketingDailyMarketing InsiderBrand InsiderThom Forbes: Top of the NewsMarketing SectorsMarketing Politics WeeklyMarketing Automotive WeeklyMarketing: CPG WeeklyMarketing: D2C WeeklyMarketing: QSR WeeklyEventsEvents Home2020 Events Calendar2021 Events CalendarUpcoming EventsSearch and Performance Insider SummitDecember 9 - 10, 2020, VirtualMarketing: PoliticsJanuary 12 - 13, 2021, VirtualMediaPost All StarsJanuary 21, 2021, NYCAgency of the YearJanuary 21, 2021, NYCCreative Media AwardsJanuary 26, 2021, NYCBrand Insider Summit RetailFebruary 16 - 17, 2021, VirtualTV + Video Insider SummitMarch 2 - 3, 2021, VirtualRecently ConcludedSearch and Performance Insider SummitDecember 9 - 10, 2020, VirtualEmail Insider SummitDecember 7 - 8, 2020, VirtualBrand Insider Summit QSROctober 27 - 28, 2020, Virtual EventTV + Video Insider SummitOctober 19 - 20, 2020, VirtualEIS AwardsOctober 6, 2020, NYCOMMA AwardsOctober 5, 2020, NYCMarketing: FinancialSeptember 23 - 24, 2020, VirtualMore EventsAwardsAwards HomeMediaPost All Stars (January 21, 2021, NYC)Agency of the Year (January 21, 2021, NYC)Creative Media Awards (January 26, 2021, NYC)EIS Awards (October 6, 2020, NYC)OMMA Awards (October 5, 2020, NYC)Marketing Automotive Awards (August 11, 2020, Online)Digital Out of Home Awards (October 15, 2019, NYC)MembersBecome A MediaPost MemberSubscribe to your choice of industry specific newsletters, save $100 on conferences, search member directories, comment on stories and more. Free to qualified media, marketing and advertising professionals.Join NowMember ResourcesAll Member DirectoryManage My AccountManage My SubscriptionsMoreAdditional ResourcesFeedback Loop (Comments)Job PostingsPremium ResearchMediaPost AcademyWhitepapersWebinarsIndustry EventsAbout and ContactsAbout MediaPostContact EditorialPrivacy/TermsMedia KitSearchAdvanced Search
Sign inUsernamePasswordRemember meForgot your password?RegisterAdvertiseFollowPrivacy Policy
MediaPost and its Affiliate websites have a firm commitment to protecting your privacy. We operate our website under the following guidelines to safeguard our users' personal information. We may revise our policy from time to time, so please check this page periodically. Personal/Company InformationUpdating or Opting OutCookiesLinks to Other SitesSecurity PrecautionsRefunds/ReturnsShippingPersonal/Company Information
To operate our services, MediaPost Communications asks for personal and company information in the member's registration form, such as your name, title, your company name, company address, and other company only identifying information. We do this, for example, when you register your company (or yourself) as a MediaPost Member on our site. We use this individual company information to deliver member only newsletters, and other service-related purposes only your company contact information is made available to other members in the member directory. MediaPost Communications may also automatically collect information such as your web browser type or IP address. This information is used to ensure our website displays properly on most commonly used browsers. This information is also used to help identify you on the service and to gather broad demographic information.Updating or Opting Out
If you want to change or update your registration information please visit www.mediapost.com and select 'my profile' from the menu, and update your information. If you would like to opt-out as a member of MediaPost Communications, please send an email to remove@mediapost.com or call us at 212-204-2000. We will delete you from our database.  Updating or Opting Out
If you want to change or update your registration information please visit www.mediapost.com and select 'my profile' from the menu, and update your information. If you would like to opt-out as a member of MediaPost Communications, choose the 'End your MediaPost Membership' option at the bottom of your profile page and click 'Save'. You will be automatically deleted from our database. If you wish to remain a MediaPost member but still want to opt-out of all email communications from us, choose the 'No Newsletters or Email Notices' option instead. If you have any questions regarding our opt-out policies, send an email to remove@mediapost.com or call us at 212-204-2000.Cookies
MediaPost Communications may place a "cookie" in the browser files of your computer. A cookie is a file that identifies you as a unique user. The cookie itself does not contain any individual information about you, although it will enable MediaPost Communications to relate your use of our site to information that you have specifically provided to us. We may use cookies to provide you with information, to save your password so that you do not have to re-enter it each time you visit our site, for retaining you selections between screens during a session, and for other purposes. The first time you register on to our site, you may be asked to accept a cookie. The cookie will remember your user name and password every time you access the site. You do not need to accept this cookie to use our services, but you will have to enter your name and password every time you visit the site. Links to Other Sites
Our site contains links to other sites outside our service. These other sites may send cookies to users, collect data, or solicit individual information. These sites or services also have separate data and privacy practices. MediaPost Communications and its Affilliate websites disclaim any responsibility or liability for their policies or actions. In general, when we link to other sites, we do not pass your personal information to those sites. In addition, MediaPost Communications offers services in conjunction with partner companies. In order to provide these co-branded services to you, we may share your personal information with our partner company. If you do not want your data to be shared, you can choose not to allow the transfer by not using that particular service. Security Precautions
We have taken careful measures to secure your information. This website has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. Our registration areas and Members' areas have SSL protection. Verisign has supplied us with a digital certificate for our website. All personal and company data referring to account applications and registration is kept in strictest confidence and security. Your individual MediaPost user information is password protected. We recommend that you do not share your password with anyone. While MediaPost Communications strives to protect your individual information, we cannot guarantee the security of any information that you transmit to MediaPost Communications and you are solely responsible for maintaining the secrecy of any passwords or other account information. MediaPost Communications will NOT disclose any personal information except as described above, as required by law or to protect our interests. MediaPost Communications does disclose user information, including demographic data, in an aggregated form that does not identify individual users in order to describe its services to prospective partners, advertisers and other third parties and for other lawful purposes. If at any time you believe that MediaPost Communications has not adhered to these principles, please notify us promptly by email to mark.kecko@mediapost.com, or via our contact informations below. Refunds/Returns
Refunds are not available unless otherwise stated at time of purchase. Shipping
Shipping charges are specified at time of purchase and are the full responsiblity of the member unless otherwise stated at time of purchase.Domestic (USA only) shipping charges for the monthly print magazines are included as part of the subscription, all other products and services are stated at time of purchase.MediaPost CommunicationsPO Box 351 Wilton, CT 06897 Phone: (212) 204-2000 Fax: (212) 204-2038Kenneth Fadner Chairman, Publisherken@mediapost.comJeff Loechner President (212) 204-2001jeff@mediapost.comJoe MandeseVP & Editor-in-Chief (212) 204-2009joe@mediapost.comSteve SmithVP-Editorial Director, Eventsstevesmith@mediapost.comAll other Editorial ContactsClick here for list of contactsJon WhitfieldSVP, Chief Revenue Officer(212) 204-2025jon@mediapost.comSeth Oilman VP, Sales & Marketing (212) 204-2012seth@mediapost.comJonathan McEwan Creative Director (212) 204-2015jonnymack@mediapost.comMark KeckoDirector of Technology (212) 204-2002mark.kecko@mediapost.comAbout MediaPostMediaKitContact EditorialRSS FeedsSitemapPrivacy/Terms & Conditions
©2020 MediaPost Communications. All rights reserved.
PO Box 351, Wilton, CT 06897
tel. 212-204-2000, fax 917-591-3261, feedback@mediapost.com   Google+All content published by MediaPost is determined by our editors 100% in the interest of our readers ... independent of advertising, sponsorships or other considerations.
